Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2016; 108492
  - Subseries III:A: Constitution and Minutes, 1972-1997; 110130
    - Minutes: Negotiating Committee, 1972; 110132 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Minutes: Pension Committee, 1976; 110131 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Subseries III:B: Officers and Staff Files, 1926-2009; 378005
    - Sub Subseries III:B:1: Aaron Alexander Files, 1948-1997, 109753
      - Adjuncts, undated, 1973-1978; 110129 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Adjuncts, 1979-1983; 110128 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Adjuncts, 1984-1989; 110127 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Admissions, 1974, 1978; 110126 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Adult Education, undated, 1973-1979; 110125 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Adult Education, 1980-1982; 110124 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Adult Education, 1983-1997; 110123 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Advertising Agencies, 1974-1981; 110122 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Advertising Campaign, 1978; 110121 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Advertising Proposal, 1979; 110120 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Agency Fee, 1971-1990; 110119 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Agreements, undated, 1969-1976; 110118 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Agreements, 1977-1984; 110117 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Agreements, 1987-1994; 110116 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Alexander, Aaron, 1977-1979; 110115 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Alumni Studies, 1974-1978; 110114 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), undated, 1971-1981; 110113 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - AAUP, 1982, 1985-1983; 110112 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - AAUP, 1984-1985; 110111 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - AAUP, 1986-1989; 110110 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - AFL-CIO (NY State & National), 1973-1978; 110109 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - AFSCME, DC 37, 1975-1986, 1995; 110108 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), undated, 1979; 110107 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - AFT, 1984-1986; 110106 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - AFT: Convention, 1974; 110105 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Arbitration, undated, 1978-1979; 110104 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Arbitration Awards, 1972-1977; 110103 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Arbitration Awards, undated; 110102 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Arbitration Awards, 1979-1985; 110101 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Associations/Organizations: General, 1974-1985; 110100 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Baruch College Chapter, undated, 1970-1979; 110099 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Baruch College Chapter, 1980-1989; 110098 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Bio: Campbell, Claude, 1984-1986; 110097 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Bio: Chapey, Geraldine, 1988; 110096 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Bio: Jones, Howard, 1986-1995; 110095 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Bio: Kugler, Israel, undated, 1987-1992; 110094 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Bio: Leberstein, Stephen, 1978; 110093 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Bio: Polishook, Irwin, 1985-1998; 110092 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Bio: Shanker, Albert, 1971-1989; 110091 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Bio: Starling, Marion, 1979-1994; 110090 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Bio: Yellowitz, Irwin, 1981-1987; 110089 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Bio's: Chapter Chairpersons, 1973-1992; 110088 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Bio's: Miscellaneous, 1982-1997; 110087 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Board of Higher Education, undated, 1972-1988; 110086 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) Chapter, 1980-1985; 110085 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - BMCC Chapter, 1986-1989; 110084 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - BMCC: PSC Grievances, undated, 1971-1976; 110083 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - BMCC: PSC Grievances, 1977-1982; 110082 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Bronx Community College, undated, 1976-1988; 110081 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Brooklyn College, undated, 1971-1977; 110080 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Brooklyn College, 1978-1979; 110079 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Brooklyn College, 1980-1984; 110078 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Brooklyn College, 1985-1986; 110077 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Brooklyn Educational Opportunity Center, undated, 1977-1989; 110076 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Budget Constraints Survey (I), 1991; 110075 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Budget Constraints Survey (II), 1991; 110074 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Budget (PSC), undated, 1970-1977; 110073 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Budget (PSC), 1978-1984; 110072 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Budget (PSC), 1985-1988; 110071 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Budget (PSC), 1989-1992; 110070 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Budget Questionnaire, 1988; 110069 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Budget Questionnaire (I), 1989; 110068 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Budget Questionnaire (II), 1989; 110067 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Business and Education, undated, 1977-1980; 110066 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Calendar, 1970-1971, 1976; 110065 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Career Education, undated, 1976-1977; 110064 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Central Office Chapter, 1975-1986; 110063 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Chapter Chairpersons, undated, 1967, 1980-1981; 110062 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Chapters: Pankin Memos, 1980; 110061 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - City College, undated, 1970-1982; 110060 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - City College, 1983-1986; 110059 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - City College: Internships in Labor Relations, 1983-1991; 110058 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1975; 110057 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1976; 110056 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1977; 110055 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1977; 110054 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1978; 110053 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1978; 110052 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1979; 110051 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1980; 110050 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1980; 110049 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1981; 110048 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1982; 110047 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1983; 110046 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1983; 110045 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - CUNY: Budget (III), 1983; 110044 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1984; 110043 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1984; 110042 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1985; 110041 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1986; 110040 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1987; 110039 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1987; 110038 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - CUNY: Budget (III), 1987; 110037 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1988; 110036 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1988; 110035 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1989; 110034 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - CUNY Courier, undated; 110033 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - CUNY Plans, 1972-1975; 110032 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1976; 110031 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1976; 110030 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1977; 110029 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1977; 110028 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1978; 110027 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1978; 110026 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1979; 110025 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1979; 110024 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1980; 110023 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1980-1983; 110022 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - CUNY Plans, 1981-1985; 110021 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - CUNY Plans, 1988-1989; 110020 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Clarion, undated, 1970-1973; 110019 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Clarion, 1974-1975; 110018 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Clarion, 1976-1977; 110017 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Clarion, 1978-1979; 110016 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Clarion, 1980; 110015 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Clarion, 1981; 110014 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Clarion, 1982-1983; 110013 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Clarion, 1984-1986, 1993-1994; 110012 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Co-affiliates, undated; 110011 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Co-affiliates, 1972-1978; 110010 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Co-affiliates, 1979-1983; 110009 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - College Laboratory Technicians, 1972-1990; 110008 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - College of Staten Island, undated, 1976-1979; 110007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - College of Staten Island, 1980-1989; 110006 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1978-1981; 110005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Committee for Public Higher Education (CPHE), undated, 1975-1978; 110004 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - CPHE, 1979-1982; 110003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - CPHE, 1983-1989; 110002 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Committee on Public Education (COPE), undated, 1974-1989; 110001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - COPE, PSC/CUNY, undated, 1976, 1985-1990; 110000 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Comptroller's Reports, undated; 109999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Comptroller's Reports, 1979-1981; 109998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Comptroller's Reports, 1982-1985; 109997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Complaints and Fan Mail, undated, 1971-1995; 109996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Computers in Instruction Conference, 1984; 109995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Program, undated, 1974-1979; 109994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Constitution, 1990, 1993; 109993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1978; 109992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1979; 109991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1980; 109990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1981; 109989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1982; 109988 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1983; 109987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1984; 109986 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 1985; 109985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Counselors, undated, 1974-1988; 109984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Disabled Booklet, 1987; 109983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Discrimination Issues, Multiculturalism, and Related Topics, 1976-1988; 109982 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Discrimination Issues, Multiculturalism, and Related Topics, 1989-1992; 109981 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Distinguished Professors, 1971-1987; 109980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Drafts, 1980; 109979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Drafts, 1981; 109978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Drafts, 1982; 109977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Dues, undated, 1978-1989; 109976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Elections, 1973-1975; 109975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Elections, 1976; 109974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Elections, 1977; 109973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Elections, 1978; 109972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Elections, 1980; 109971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Elections, 1981-1982; 109970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Elections, 1983-1986; 109969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Elections: Materials, 1988; 109968 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Elections (PSC), undated, 1969-1979; 109967 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Elections (PSC), 1980-1989; 109966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Enrollment, undated; 109965 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Experimental Program/Research in Education, 1969-1978; 109964 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Facilities, undated, 1973-1975; 109963 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Facilities, 1976-1978, 1986; 109962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Faculty Development Program, undated, 1977-1985; 109961 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Faculty Development Program, 1986-1987; 109960 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Faculty Development Program, 1988-1989; 109959 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Faculty Development Program: Participants' Evaluation Forms, 1985-1986; 109958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Faculty Research Award Program, undated, 1970-1980; 109957 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Faculty Research Award Program, 1984-1990; 109956 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Faculty Senate Minutes, etc., 1985-1986; 109955 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Faculty Senate Minutes, etc., 1987-1988; 109954 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Federal Credit Union, 1980-1988; 109953 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Finance Committee, 1976-1990; 109952 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Financial Disclosure, undated, 1974-1993; 109951 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Fiscal Crisis (NYC), 1975-1989; 109950 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - General Equivalency Diploma, 1980-1986; 109949 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Governance (CUNY), undated, 1974-1985; 109948 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Graduate Center, 1973-1987; 109947 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Graduate Programs, undated, 1970-1995; 109946 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Grants for Faculty, 1977, 1994; 109945 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Grievances, 1977-1979; 109944 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Grievances, undated, 1980-1981; 109943 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Grievances, 1982-1993; 109942 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Grievances and Arbitrations, undated, 1975-1977; 109941 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Health and Safety, undated, 1974-1982; 109940 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Health and Safety, 1985-1986; 109939 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Health and Safety, 1987; 109938 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Health and Safety, 1988-1989; 109937 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Higher Education, undated, 1978-1979; 109936 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Hostos College, undated, 1974-1979; 109935 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Hostos College, 1980-1989; 109934 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Hotline, 1978-1979; 109933 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Howe, Harold, 1978; 109932 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Howe Report, undated; 109931 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Howe Report, undated, 1973-1979; 109930 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Hunter College, 1972-1979; 109929 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Hunter College Chapter, 1980-1989; 109928 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Hunter College Chapter: Burks, David, 1978-1984; 109927 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Internship in Labor Studies, 1978, 1983-1984; 109926 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Internship in Labor Studies, 1987-1989; 109925 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Italian-American Studies (Calandra), 1977; 109924 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Jewish Labor Committee, 1976-1979; 109923 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Jobs and the University Conference, undated, 1977-1978; 109922 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Jobs and the University Conference: Transcript, 1978; 109921 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - John Jay College, undated, 1978-1989; 109920 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Kingsborough Community College Chapter, undated, 1971-1983; 109919 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Kingsborough Community College Chapter, 1984-1991; 109918 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Labor Studies, undated, 1977-1979; 109917 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - LaGuardia Community College, undated, 1971-1989; 109916 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Lane, Fred: Paper on Higher Education, 1986; 109915 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Legislative, undated, 1975-1979; 109914 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Legislative, 1980-1985; 109913 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Legislative, 1986-1989; 109912 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Legislative Conference, undated, 1954-1970; 109911 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Legislative Conference, 1971-1976; 109910 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Lehman College, undated, 1973-1978; 109909 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Lehman College, 1979-1989; 109908 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Levinstein, Aaron, 1981-1986; 109907 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Library Association of City University (LACUNY), undated, 1970-1972; 109906 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - LACUNY, 1974-1977; 109905 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - LACUNY, 1979-1983; 109904 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - LACUNY, 1986-1989; 109903 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Lobbying (AFT), undated, 1974-1982; 109902 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Making It Through College, 1984; 109901 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Making It Through College: Promotion and Distribution, 1980-1985; 109900 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Management (CUNY), undated, 1976-1985; 109899 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Manhattan Educational Opportunity Center, undated; 109898 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Manual of Policy (BHE), 1973; 109897 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Medgar Evers College, 1970-1989; 109896 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Medical School, 1985-1994; 109895 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Member Services, undated, 1970-1986; 109894 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Membership Figures, 1973-1974; 109893 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Membership Mailings, undated, 1971-1989; 109892 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Membership to 1989, undated, 1973-1989; 109891 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Merger, undated, 1967-1974, 1984; 109890 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1977; 109889 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Municipal Labor Coalition, undated, 1975-1977; 109888 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Municipal Labor Coalition, 1978-1979; 109887 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Municipal Labor Coalition, 1980-1988; 109886 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - National Education Association (NEA), 1974, 1980-1985; 109885 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - National Education Association (NEA), 1986-1989; 109884 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Negotiations, 1976-1977; 109883 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Negotiations, 1978; 109882 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Negotiations: Notes, 1977; 109881 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - New York City Central Labor Council, 1976-1985; 109880 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - New York City Community League, undated, 1971-1980; 109879 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - New York City: General, 1977-1990; 109878 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - New York City Technical College, undated, 1979-1989; 109877 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - New York Educators Association (NYEA), 1975-1977; 109876 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - New York Educators Association (NYEA), 1978-1986; 109875 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), 1970-1979; 109874 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT), 1971-1984; 109873 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - NYSUT, 1985-1989; 109872 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Office of Admissions Services, undated, 1976-1980; 109871 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Office of Admissions Services, 1981-1987; 109870 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Opportunity U. Ad Campaign, undated, 1977-1979; 109869 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Opportunity U.: Fan Mail, undated, 1978-1979; 109868 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Opportunity U.: Finances, undated, 1978-1979; 109867 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Opportunity U.: Samples, 1978-1980; 109866 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Pensions, undated, 1970-1986; 109865 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Polishook Articles, 1976-1987; 109864 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Polishook-Nielsen Articles, undated; 109863 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Press Associations, 1976-1982; 109862 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases, undated, 1970-1980; 109861 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Private Colleges, 1975-1980; 109860 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Professional Development, undated, 1974-1988; 109859 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Professional Staff Congress (PSC): Ads, 1975-1990; 109858 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - PSC: History, undated, 1948-1971; 109857 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - PSC: History, 1972-1975; 109856 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - PSC: History (I), 1976; 109855 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - PSC: History (II), 1976; 109854 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - PSC: History (III), 1976; 109853 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - PSC: History, 1978-1990; 109852 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - PSC: History (Clarion Articles), 1981-1982; 109851 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - PSC/Home Office, 1984-1985; 109850 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Professional Staff Union: Bargaining, 1973-1979; 109849 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Professional Staff Union: Bargaining, 1980-1982; 109848 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Promotional Material, undated, 1972-1980; 109847 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Public Relations, undated, 1972-1989; 109846 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Queensborough Community College, undated, 1967-1978; 109845 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Queensborough Community College, 1979-1990; 109844 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Queens College, undated, 1973-1979; 109843 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Queens College, 1980-1982; 109842 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Queens College, 1983-1989; 109841 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Reasonable Accommodations, undated, 1988-1989; 109840 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Reasonable Accommodations: 2nd Edition, undated, 1988-1996; 109839 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Reasonable Accommodations: Original and Other Versions, 1990-1995; 109838 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Reasonable Accommodations: Permission to Duplicate/Reprint, 1988-1996; 109837 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Reasonable Accommodations: Requests, 1992-1995; 109836 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Recruitment, undated, 1972-1989; 109835 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Reductions in Instructional Programs Questionnaire (I), 1989-1990; 109834 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Reductions in Instructional Programs Questionnaire (II), 1989-1990; 109833 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Regents, undated; 109832 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Regents, 1979; 109831 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Regents, 1980; 109830 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Regents, 1981-1983; 109829 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Regents, 1984-1986; 109828 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Regents, 1987-1988; 109827 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Regents Master Plan, undated, 1978-1980; 109826 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Registrars, 1975-1983; 109825 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Research Foundation, 1985; 109824 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Research Foundation Chapter, 1973-1984; 109823 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Research Foundation Chapter, 1985; 109822 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Research Foundation Chapter, 1986-1989; 109821 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Residency, 1975-1981; 109820 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Retirees, undated, 1974-1978; 109819 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Retirement (Mandatory), undated, 1977-1991; 109818 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Retrenchment, undated, 1974-1975; 109817 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Retrenchment (I), 1976; 109816 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Retrenchment (II), 1976; 109815 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Retrenchment, 1977-1979; 109814 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Retrenchment, 1980-1983; 109813 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Retrenchment Case, 1976-1978; 109812 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Sabbaticals, 1971-1975; 109811 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Salaries, undated, 1973-1974; 109810 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Salaries, 1975-1976; 109809 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Salaries, 1977-1978; 109808 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Salaries, 1979; 109807 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Salaries, 1981-1985; 109806 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Salaries, 1986-1989; 109805 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Schools of General Studies, 1971-1977; 109804 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Solicitations, 1981-1989; 109803 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Speeches/Statements, undated, 1974-1976; 109802 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Speeches/Statements, 1977-1978; 109801 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Speeches/Statements, 1979-1989; 109800 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Staff Development Program, 1988; 109799 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Standards and Basic Skills, etc., 1974-1997; 109798 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Statistical Data, undated; 109797 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Student Association of SUNY (SASU), 1976-1982; 109796 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Student Lobbying, 1983-1985; 109795 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Student Senate, undated, 1968-1986; 109794 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Summer Hours, 1971-1977; 109793 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - TAP Program - Part Time Legislation, 1977-1982; 109792 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Teaching at CUNY, 1987-1989; 109791 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Teaching Load Analysis, 1987; 109790 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Television and Radio, 1972-1991; 109789 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Tenure, 1978; 109788 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Tenure Quotas, undated, 1972-1983; 109787 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Tuition, 1973-1977; 109786 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Tuition: Tax Credits, etc., undated, 1974-1978; 109785 (Box 32, Folder 13)